But if you look here, I'm taking a lot less damage from the tower now, because I have a lot of armor.
That doesn't mean the towers are physical and not magic.
I always do deal with physical damage.
Now, one more thing. Are you ready?
Magic resist. These are also tank items, so surely it'll make me, you know, take a bunch of damage, right?
For magic! Only magic. No physical damage.
Well, aside from the extra HP you got.
And this is so, so, so important because so many players, even after a year or two years of playing,
they'll be against a team of full, you know, armor, like physical damage characters,
and they'll be building magic resist, right?
Players that have been playing the game for two years.
And so for the kids to learn this at the very beginning, it's so, yeah, it's so good.